=No.9 Hunter=
=Episode 11=
Ah.
You wretched Yu Linjun!
Once I break the Stone Curse
and fuse with the Stone's power,
I'll tear you apart!
Who are you looking for, goddess?
You can tell me.
We Xuanwu Sect's network
spans the world.
We can help you find him.
Who are you, by the way?
Stop with the "goddess" already.
It's so cringey.
Gives me the creeps.
My name is Zhu Yu.
This is a family heirloom.
With this,
I can find whoever you're looking for.
Consider it thanks for saving
the little dog demon and me.
Ah!
Young Master Zhu,
that was completely coincidence.
It was nothing.
No need to thank us.
My father always said
one must repay kindness.
You saved me.
I must thank you.
Especially you, Goddess Ziyan.
A good deed needs no reward.
We shouldn't take
what's precious to you.
Please take it back.
Please...
Ah!
To be honest,
Goddess Ziyan,
the moment you appeared,
I knew for certain
you were the one
I've been searching for.
This is
my family's Five Spirits Pendant.
It brings good fortune to its bearer.
Think of it
as my betrothal gift.
(Hmm?)
(This pendant is actually...)
Hmm?
This is hardly proper.
Besides, you already have a rouge box.
Take it back.
Ah.
Seriously,
what are you two doing? Reciting poetry?
All that mumbling.
So annoying.
Just go, go, go!
In this life,
I've chosen you.
It seems
our Ruyi Pavilion
will be making a match.
The Purestone Bloom.
Hmm.
Where did you see it?
Why is it embroidered here?
So
this is called Purestone Bloom.
What a beautiful name.
But I promised him
I wouldn't tell anyone.
Him?
Who is he?
I'm afraid I can't say.
The reason I have a foothold
in the Wilds of Lize
is my reputation for trust.
I hope you understand.
However,
I can give you a piece of information
from the deepest part
of the Wilds of Lize.
Worth a fortune.
You'll give it to me for free?
Why?
Maybe
because the moment I saw you,
I inexplicably took a liking to you.
Maybe
we have a past-life connection.
The Divine Stone is hidden
in the deepest part.
(If there's a Stone
in the Wilds of Lize,)
(does that mean I'm not the only one?)
Thank you.
Thanks.
What do you think of Young Master Zhu?
Top-tier.
Give me specifics. How is he top-tier?
He is the heir of Xuanwu Sect.
Status.
Position.
Wealth.
Looks.
So you are saying
our little junior
will accept his proposal?
Quite likely.
Zhu Yu is the best choice for her.
Traitor.
What do you think, Yuanchu?
After the sky is mended,
she will be free.
In the future,
she will meet many more outstanding men.
Maybe one day, she'll fall for someone
and find her own happiness.
That would be a good thing.
Yuanchu,
how can you give up
before you've even tried?
You're the future Sect Master
of Yuanzhen.
You have better looks,
better skills,
better everything.
You and her would be perfect.
Don't you think?
Not necessarily.
If the love is real,
does it really need every waking moment?
You should suffer a little
for love, too.
A little suffering builds character.
That's how you rise above the rest.
Yuanchu,
I really think she's great.
Even though she is a demon,
she is a genuinely good one.
Her personality
balances yours perfectly.
I support this match.
Thank you, Senior.
Hmm.
I see it now.
Yes, yes, yes!
That is exactly it!
I need to press forward.
Bolder with every fall.
No.
I disagree.
We should bring Young Master Zhu along.
More people, more strength, right?
Wonderful! Goddess Ziyan,
you're finally letting me close to you!
Stop calling me "goddess."
It gives me the creeps.
Just call me by my name.
Okay, Ziyan.
Then you can just call me Yuyu.
Do not be so formal
with "Young Master Zhu."
Yuyu?
Hmm.
Yu.
Yuyuyu.
Hmm.
Sounds like a "Yoo-hoo" to call a horse!
See?
She doesn't love you.
She's just a fickle demoness
messing around with other men.
Once the sky is sealed,
kill her at once!
(If she does not love me,)
(could I actually kill her?)
Hehe.
(But...)
(why does watching her
with someone else)
(feel so...)
(terrible?)
Ziyan.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
My old ailment just flared up.
Please step out for a moment.
I need to rest.
Oh, okay.
I'll go find a physician.
Ah!
No, you can't leave.
You need to use your power to help me.
Why aren't you saying anything?
You don't want to?
No, I don't.
I just...
Ugh, forget it.
Men are so petty and dramatic.
Is this because of Zhu Yu?
Are you sulking?
I said I am not.
Fine.
I will channel...
channel my power to suppress it for you.
No.
I don't like it.
You don't like what?
I don't like you talking to him.
I don't like you saying his name.
I don't like you eating with him.
I don't like the way you look at him.
I don't like you smiling at him.
I don't like everything between you two,
because I like you.
Are you jealous?
No, I'm not.
Are you still mad now?
How about now?
Ah.
♪I drink the rain of this mortal world,
and seek the path I chose♪
♪How much sorrow and joy have I known?♪
♪With this flesh and blood,
I chase the distant light♪
♪Just to see clearly
the memories of this drifting life♪
♪Let the wind sweep away
this heavy air of sorrow♪
♪Do not forget the tangled paths
that you and I have crossed♪
♪Let towering waves come crashing down;
I'll fight against the tide♪
♪I shatter the hollow fate
they wrote for me♪
♪With a heart free of regret,
I'll face the heavens and earth♪